anythinginit.com 2011-12-12

# AnythinginIT.com - Buy online Computer and IT products at the lowest price in India.

|  | Welcome Guest! |   Sign In  |  |  My Account  |  | My Cart   | [](http://www.anythinginit.com/ "Home") | [](mailto:info@anythinginit.com "Contact Us") |   
---|---|---|---|---|---|---  
| 

|   
---|---  
---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---  
| 

|   
---  
My Facebook Login Page Login with Facebook  
  
|   Your are here: Home >Privacy Policy   
---  
|  |  |   
---|---|---  
  |  |  **Privacy & Security**  
---  
****Anything _in_ IT**. ** _com_** **  
  
We understand the importance of your privacy, hence we have created the following Privacy and Security Policy, where you can know, when you visit our website ****Anything _in_ IT**. ** _com_**** what information we collect, why we collect it, and how & where we use it. This Privacy Policy also addresses our data security practices, the options you have to access and control any personally identifiable information you provide to us, and other matters. 

When you use our website, we may request your name, street address, telephone numbers, email ID or other information. We use this information to complete and support your purchases & queries you made on ****Anything _in_ IT**. ** _com_**** website, for internal purposes and to comply with any requirements of law. This information may be disclosed to our staff and to third parties involved in the completion of your transaction & queries, the delivery of your order or the support of your use of the ****Anything _in_ IT**. ** _com_**** web site. With your consent, we may also share your information with trusted third party marketing partners. We may also use this to inform you any news, new arrival or happenings in the market.   
  
**We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.**  
  
As you browse our web site, we may gather navigational data & IP address that shows what pages are visited and how long various features are used. This information will not reveal your identity or be linked to you personally. We use this information to complete and support your purchases from and use of the ****Anything _in_ IT**. ** _com_**** website and to comply with any requirements of law. This information may be disclosed only to our staff and to third parties involved in the completion of your transaction, the delivery of your order and the support of your use of the ****Anything _in_ IT**. ** _com_**** website.   
  
your information if necessary to protect our legal rights, if the information relates to actual or threatened harmful conduct, or ****Anything _in_ IT**. ** _com_**** has good faith belief that such action is necessary to (1) conform to the requirements of law or comply with governmental orders, court orders, or legal process served on ****Anything _in_ IT**. ** _com_**** or (2) to protect and defend the property or rights of ****Anything _in_ IT**. ** _com_**** , the users of its website or the public. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for fraud protection and credit risk protection. If ****Anything _in_ IT**. ** _com_**** should ever file for bankruptcy or merge with another company, we may sell the information you provide to us on the ****Anything _in_ IT**. ** _com_**** website to a third party or share your personal information with the company we merge with.  
  
are very tiny text files that are stored on your computer when you visit certain web pages that record your preferences. ****Anything _in_ IT**. ** _com_**** uses cookies to keep track of what you have in your shopping cart and to remember you when you return to our store. They cannot harm your computer and they do not contain any personal or private information. You must accept cookies to shop at ****Anything _in_ IT**. ** _com_**** . We offer secure web pages to collect certain kinds of user information and we store certain kinds of data in encrypted form. We follow reasonable technical and management practices to help protect the confidentiality, security and integrity of data stored on our system. While no computer system is completely secure, we believe the measures implemented by our web site reduce the likelihood of security problems to a level appropriate to the type of data involved. ****Anything _in_ IT**. ** _com_**** uses Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), an encryption technology that works with Netscape Navigator, Microsoft Internet Explorer, and some other browsers, so that only ****Anything _in_ IT**. ** _com_**** can read a customer's personal information.   
  
This Site contains links to third party websites, including sites of manufacturers or any other advertisers. ****Anything _in_ IT**. ** _com_**** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. Your use of these third party websites is entirely at your own risk.   
  
By using the ****Anything _in_ IT**. ** _com_**** website, you agree to this Privacy and Security Policy. This is our entire and exclusive Privacy and Security Policy and it supersedes any earlier version. We may change our Privacy and Security Policy by posting a new version of the policy on this page which it is your responsibility to review frequently.   
  
**LEGAL DISCLAIMER:**  
This Site operates AS-IS and AS-AVAILABLE, without liability of any kind. We do not claim the information & MRP of the product is correct, we have gathered data from various sources & tried to validate also but we are not responsible for any error in the same. We are not responsible for events beyond our direct control. Any legal actions against us must be commenced in Mumbai within one month after the claim arose, or be barred.   
  
If you have a privacy question about the ****Anything _in_ IT**. ** _com_**** ** __** web site, please email: [Customer Service ](mailto:Support@AnythinginIT.com) or call us at +91-22-40686868   
  
>  

|  |   
|  [  
](http://www.anythinginit.com/toolbar.asp)  

[  
](http://www.anythinginit.com/)  
  
---  
|  |  |  |  |  |  |  |   
---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---  
| About Us | |  Payment Policy | | Faq | | New Visitors | | Quick Guide | | Shipping Charges | | My Account | | Feedback | | Contact Us | | Bookmark  
---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---  
  |   | Disclaimer |  |Privacy Policy | | Warranty Terms |  | Return Policy |  | Engineer Register |  | We Cater |   |    
Categories : [Laptop ](http://www.anythinginit.com/products.asp?scpk=2) [Dekstop Server ](http://www.anythinginit.com/products.asp?scpk=1)[ Life Style Products](http://www.itct.in/lsp/) [Cabinets ](http://www.anythinginit.com/products.asp?scpk=49) [CPUs / Processors](http://www.anythinginit.com/products.asp?scpk=32) [Graphics Cards](http://www.anythinginit.com/products.asp?scpk=46) [Hard Disk / Storage Solutions](http://www.anythinginit.com/products.asp?scpk=18) [iPod MP3 MP4 Player](http://www.anythinginit.com/products.asp?scpk=252)  [Keyboard](http://www.anythinginit.com/products.asp?scpk=50)  [LCD & CRT Monitors](http://www.anythinginit.com/products.asp?scpk=52)  [RAM / Memories](http://www.anythinginit.com/products.asp?scpk=10)  [Motherboard](http://www.anythinginit.com/products.asp?scpk=5)  [Mouse](http://www.anythinginit.com/products.asp?scpk=51)  [Networking Routers](http://www.anythinginit.com/products.asp?scpk=59)  [ODD FDD](http://www.anythinginit.com/products.asp?scpk=47)  [Other Accessories](http://www.anythinginit.com/products.asp?scpk=31)  [PDA / Mobile](http://www.anythinginit.com/products.asp?scpk=58)  [Pendrives Flash Cards](http://www.anythinginit.com/products.asp?scpk=108)  [Power Supply (SMPS)](http://www.anythinginit.com/products.asp?scpk=158)  [Dot Matrix Printers](http://www.anythinginit.com/products.asp?scpk=173)  [Laser & InkJet Printers](http://www.anythinginit.com/products.asp?scpk=54)  [Projectors](http://www.anythinginit.com/products.asp?scpk=204)  [Scanners](http://www.anythinginit.com/products.asp?scpk=55)  [Security Systems -CCTV](http://www.anythinginit.com/products.asp?scpk=275)  [Security Systems -DVR](http://www.anythinginit.com/products.asp?scpk=276)  [Softwares](http://www.anythinginit.com/products.asp?scpk=61)  [Speakers Headphones](http://www.anythinginit.com/products.asp?scpk=53)  [Time & Attendance System](http://www.anythinginit.com/products.asp?scpk=291)  [TV Tunner Cards](http://www.anythinginit.com/products.asp?scpk=57)  [UPS](http://www.anythinginit.com/products.asp?scpk=157)  [Web Cam / Digital Cam](http://www.anythinginit.com/products.asp?scpk=56)    
**Stores** : [AntiVirus ](http://www.anythinginit.com/products.asp?scpk=191)| [Acer ](http://www.anythinginit.com/acer/)| [AMD ](http://www.anythinginit.com/AMD/)| [APC ](http://www.anythinginit.com/APC/)| [Apple](http://www.anythinginit.com/Apple/)  | [Asus](http://www.anythinginit.com/Asus/)  | [ATI](http://www.anythinginit.com/ATI/)  | [Benq](http://www.anythinginit.com/Benq/)  | [Canon](http://www.anythinginit.com/Canon/)  | [Compaq](http://www.anythinginit.com/Compaq/)  | [CoolerMaster](http://www.anythinginit.com/CoolerMaster/)  | [Creative](http://www.anythinginit.com/Creative/)  | [Dell](http://www.anythinginit.com/Dell/)  | [Epson](http://www.anythinginit.com/Epson/)  | [Fujitsu](http://www.anythinginit.com/Fujitsu/)  | [Gigabyte](http://www.anythinginit.com/Gigabyte/)  | [HP](http://www.anythinginit.com/HP/)  | [iBall](http://www.anythinginit.com/iBall/)  | [IBM](http://www.anythinginit.com/IBM/)  | [Kingston](http://www.anythinginit.com/Kingston/)  | [LaCie](http://www.anythinginit.com/LaCie/)  | [Quadro](http://www.anythinginit.com/Leadtek/)  | [Lenovo](http://www.anythinginit.com/Lenovo/)  | [LG](http://www.anythinginit.com/LG/)  | [Linksys](http://www.anythinginit.com/Linksys/)  | [Logitech](http://www.anythinginit.com/Logitech/)  | [Microsoft](http://www.anythinginit.com/Microsoft/)  | [MSI](http://www.anythinginit.com/MSI/)  | [Razer](http://www.anythinginit.com/Razer/)  | [Samsung](http://www.anythinginit.com/Samsung/)  | [Sapphire](http://www.anythinginit.com/Sapphire/)  | [Seagate](http://www.anythinginit.com/Seagate/)  | [Sony](http://www.anythinginit.com/Sony/)  | [Tagan](http://www.anythinginit.com/Tagan/)  | [Tally](http://www.anythinginit.com/Tally/)  | [Targus](http://www.anythinginit.com/Targus/)  | [Toshiba](http://www.anythinginit.com/Toshiba/)  | [Transcend](http://www.anythinginit.com/Transcend/)  | [ViewSonic](http://www.anythinginit.com/ViewSonic/)  | [WD](http://www.anythinginit.com/WesternDigital/)  | [XFX](http://www.anythinginit.com/XFX/)  | [Zotac](http://www.anythinginit.com/Zotac/)  
**Services :**[Domain Name Registration](http://www.anythinginit.com/domain/) | [Web Hosting Services](http://domain.anythinginit.com/hosting.php) | [Free Virus Check](http://www.stopvirusnow.com/)   
**Corporate Office** : 2nd Floor, Dhanashree Building, P.G. Solanki Path, GrantRoad (E), Mumbai: 400007. Maharshtra. India. **Help Line: +91 97 69 40 68 68**  
**Branches** : **West** : Ahmedabad, Aurangabad, Baroda, Bhopal, Goa, Indore, Jabalpur, Mumbai Lamington Road, Thane, Nagpur, Nashik, Pune, Raipur, Rajkot, Surat. **South** : Bangalore, Calicut. Chennai, Cochin, Coimbatore, Hubli, Kottayam, Madurai, Mangalore, Pondicherry, Secunderabad, Trivandrum, Vijaywada, Vizag. **North** : Agra, Amritsar, Chandigarh, Dehradun, Delhi, Gaziabad, Gorakhpur, Gurgaon, Hisar, Haldwani, Jaipur, Jammu, Jodhpur, Lucknow, Ludhiana, Parwanoo,Varanasi. **East** : Bhubaneshwar, Guwahati, Kolkatta, Patna, Ranchi, Siliguri.   
Copyright 2011-2012, **AnythinginIT.com** , All Rights Reserved.
